quizzes:
  - category: "Flags - Top 50 Economy Countries"
    questions:
      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "United States"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "United States flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "China"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "China flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Germany"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Germany flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Japan"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Japan flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "India"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "India flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "United Kingdom"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "United Kingdom flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "France"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "France flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Brazil"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Brazil flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Italy"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Italy flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Canada"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Canada flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "South Korea"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "South Korea flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Spain"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Spain flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Mexico"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Mexico flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Indonesia"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Indonesia flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Netherlands"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Netherlands flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Saudi Arabia"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Saudi Arabia flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Turkey"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Turkey flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Switzerland"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Switzerland flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Poland"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Poland flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Belgium"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Belgium flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Argentina"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Argentina flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Sweden"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Sweden flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Ireland"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Ireland flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Austria"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Austria flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Norway"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Norway flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Nigeria"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Nigeria flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Israel"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Israel flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "United Arab Emirates"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "United Arab Emirates flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Singapore"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Singapore flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Hong Kong"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Hong Kong flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Denmark"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Denmark flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Malaysia"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Malaysia flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Philippines"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Philippines flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Vietnam"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Vietnam flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Pakistan"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Pakistan flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Bangladesh"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Bangladesh flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Chile"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Chile flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Colombia"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Colombia flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Greece"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Greece flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Portugal"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Portugal flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Czech Republic"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Czech Republic flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Romania"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Romania flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Iraq"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Iraq flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Peru"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Peru flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Thailand"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Thailand flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "New Zealand"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "New Zealand flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Kuwait"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Kuwait flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Hungary"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Hungary flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Egypt"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Egypt flag"

      - question: "Which country flag is this?"
        question_media: {text: false, audio: true, image: true}
        answer: "Qatar"
        answer_media: {text: true, audio: false, image: false}
        question_image_search_term: "Qatar flag"

